ridersreviews.com 2009-06-16

# Riders Reviews - Motorcycle reviews. » Privacy Policy - Disclaimer

Disclaimer: The articles posted here are based on personal opinions from personal experiences. Consult a professional if you need advice on motorcycle related information and learning to ride, such as a motorcycle rider training facility.

Privacy Policy: As a fellow Internet user myself, I totally respect your online privacy. It goes without saying that I’m fully committed to safeguarding your online privacy while you’re here at the ridersreviews.com website. That’s precisely why I’ve decided to include the following, which discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website.

Log Files  
Like most standard websites, this website uses log files. These include: Internet Protocol addresses (IP addresses), browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc., are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Web Cookies  
Web cookies (also known as HTTP cookies, or just cookies) are parcels of text that are sent by a server to a Web browser, and then sent back unchanged by the browser each time it accesses that server. In other words, a cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s computer that is tied to information about the user.  
This website uses cookie technology for purposes of web site traffic analysis.  
Some of my business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies. This site has no access to, or control over these cookies once I’ve given permission to them to advertise on this website.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Links  
This website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that I am not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. I encourage you, when you leave this website, to read the privacy statements/policies of each and every website you visit, as this particular privacy policy applies solely to this particular website.

Advertisers  
I use outside advertising networks and companies in order to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons in order to collect data in the ad serving process. These such cookies and/or web beacons are collected by the companies and/or advertising networks, themselves. I do not have any access to this information.

Webmaster Contact Information  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding the ridersreviews.com privacy policy, please feel free to contact me at [CONTACT FORM](http://www.ridersreviews.com/contact/ "contact us").

We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time.
